

CONTACTS

- - github.com/justkwer
- instagram.com/justkwer
- - linkedin.com/in/kwer
- - t.me/justkwer
 - https://t.me/justkwer

LANGUAGES

Russian (native)

English (intermediate)

SKILS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

TypeScript

Redux / RTK / Saga

React-query

Styled Components

Next.js

REST API

Git

Three.js

ALEXI HANGULEV

Frontend Developer

ABOUTME

Frontend developer with 3+ years experience. I usually write in React and Next, I also study Three.js (I have a lot of experience in 3D modeling).

am interested in information technologies and how they transform our lives.

There's nothing better than clean code and a working application.

EXPERIENCE

- Frontend Developer at Freelance 2022-Present, Frontend
- Mogilev Energy
 2013-2022, Constructor

EDUCATION

- Self-Education 2021-Present, Frontend
- The Rolling Scopes School 2021-2022, Frontend
- Belarusian-Russian University 2008-2013, Engineer